<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contact Control on Ken&#39;s Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://KennethChao.github.io/tags/contact-control/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contact Control on Ken&#39;s Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 12:26:41 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://KennethChao.github.io/tags/contact-control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MathWorks, Safe trajectory tracking using Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://KennethChao.github.io/project/projects_intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 12:26:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KennethChao.github.io/project/projects_intern/</guid>
      <description>This is my last project at MathWorks Robotics Team (who develops the Robotics System Toolbox (RST)). Inspired by Haddadin&amp;rsquo;s famous demo, the idea is to demonstrate manipulator algorithms in RST for the safe robot-environment interaction to a ROS-enabled robot. In this project I implemented Haddadin&amp;rsquo;s time scaling method to achieve safe trajectory tracking on the Sawyer from Rethink Robotics. The purpose of this project is threefold:
 Contributed an simulation in Simulink with Simscape Multibody to showcase the usage of Robotics Manipulator Blocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS project, Walking Control under Step Height Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://KennethChao.github.io/project/project_ms_control/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:35:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KennethChao.github.io/project/project_ms_control/</guid>
      <description>This controller was degined to adapt uncertained step height. Two controllers are applied in different levels (as shown in the following figure):
 The ladning modification (triggered by impulse detection) determines the updated level height, holds the landing foot position, and switchs the state machine to double support when the impact occurs. Due to the impact, the flat contacts on both feet might break (which is not desired in double support).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>